CURRICULUM VITAE

Name Luis Salvador Aedo Sanhueza

Current Position Senior Advisor Resources Geologist, Compañía

Minera Doña Inés de Collahuasi, CMDIC

Date of Birth October 1st, 1967

NationalityChileanMarital StatusSingleDependent ChildrenNone

Languages Proficiency on both oral and written English

International Mobility No restrictions

Profile

I am a Geologist with over twenty years of experience in Copper-Gold-Silver-Uranium Mining, including Mine Operations in Copiapó and Tarapacá Region in Northern Chile and South Australia.

My responsibilities as a Geologist in several positions in different assets mainly have been:

Production Geologist, Planning and Development of Drilling Programs (Production, Infill, and Greenfield-Brownfield), surface mapping, core logging, interpretation and Resources Estimation, Geometallurgical variable analysis applied to production.

Overseeing of the Resources and Reserves technical group for Long, Mid and short term purposes.

Carry out all procedures and industry standards in conjunction with business goal and coordinating with the different operations to ensure compliance with the standards best practices and guidelines.

Additionally I have been nominated Competent Person for Anglo American, Glencore and Xstrata to sign annual statement.

I have had Contract Management responsibilities in companies like: Enaex (Explosives) and Major Drilling S.A.

Key Strengths/Attributes

- Good knowledge of Chilean copper business including different kind of deposits like porphyries, IOCG and exotic deposits.
- Multi variables estimation including among others Au, Ag, Fe, Mo, U3O8 and deleterious elements.
- Performing Geological and Geometallurgical models applied to Production requirements.
- Working together with other technical groups by creating synergies and integrations in the different processes.
- Competent Person for Resources.
- Contract Management.
- Implementation of safety procedures, Health, Environmental and Communities' Policies.

Academic Qualifications

1985-1986: Physics, Universidad Católica de Chile.

1987-1994: Geology, Universidad de Chile. (Bachelor in Geological Sciences and Geologist degree)

2006: Citation of Geostatistics applied to mining, Alberta University.

2012: Post Graduate Degree, "Management for Mining Industry", "Habilidades Gerenciales para la Industria Minera", Universidad Adolfo Ibáñez.

Work Experience

Since June 2014

Senior Advisor Collahuasi (Chile)

Key Responsibilities:

- Geometallurgical, Geotechnical modelling support.
- Interaction with different technical groups detecting opportunities and gaps in the process.
- Long, mid and short Term Geology, Modelling and Resources estimation according JORC compliance.
- Reconciliation Process.
- Preparation of Annual Statement for Resources and Reserves.
- Competent Person for Resources

Jan 2010-June 2014

Mineral Resources Superintendent Collahuasi (Chile)

Key Responsibilities:

- Leading Resources Team following Company guide lines.
- Coaching and Mentoring for senior levels.
- Long, mid and short Term Geology, Modelling and Resources estimation according JORC compliance.
- Reconciliation Process.
- Preparation of Annual Statement for Resources and Reserves
- Competent Person for Resources

April 2008-Dec 2009

Senior Resources Geologist Olympic Dam

BhpBilliton (South Australia)

Key Responsibilities:

- Link between mine geology group and ODX expansion project.
- Creation of block model for Underground purposes.
- Long Term Geologist, Geo-Geomet Modelling and Resources estimation.
- Reconciliation Process.(F3 implementation)
- Coaching and Mentoring for junior levels.

June 1997-March 2008

Long Term-Senior Geologist CMCC Cerro Colorado

BhpBilliton (Iquique)

Key Responsibilities:

- Long Term Geologist, Geo-Geomet Modelling and Resources estimation.
- Preparation of annual Resources Statement.
- Geotechnical logging, slope stability analysis, strength rock block model.
- Production Geology: Bench mapping, production and infill drill holes logging and Brownfield program, Planning and supervision of drilling programs.
- Creation of short term block model for Production purposes.
- Reconciliation process, F1 & F2.
- Generation of new exploration targets outside the final pit.

June 1996-June 1997

Production Geologist at Sociedad Minera Cascada

Pudahuel S.A (Iquique)

Key Responsibilities:

- Underground geological mapping, cuttings and diamond core logging.
- Planning and supervision of drilling programs.
- Generation of new exploration targets in the district.

Nov 1994-August 1996

Production Geologist

Punta del Cobre S.A. (Copiapó)

Key Responsibilities:

- Underground geological mapping and drill holes logging.
- Resources and Reserves estimation of the Deposit.
- Planning and supervision of drilling programs.
- Generation of new exploration targets in the district.

Practice Periods:

Cambior Exploration Chile: Field and underground mapping, quartz veins sampling for gold Challacollo I Region of Chile.

ENAP Magallanes XII Region of Chile: Cuttings logging, fluorescence analysis.

Comments

Computer skills: Microsoft office (including Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Access; intermediate and advanced level), Dips, Swedge, Acquire, Vulcan (advanced level), Datamine, Minitab, AutoCAD, Sage, Sgems, Gslib, Leapfrog.

Mine site visits:

El Salvador (porphyry copper-Codelco), Andina (porphyry copper-Codelco), El Teniente (porphyry copper-Codelco), Escondida (porphyry copper-BhpBilliton), Los Bronces (porphyry copper-Anglo American), El Sauce (Cu Skarn-Las Cenizas), Candelaria (IOCG Freeport McMoran), El Soldado (Cu strata-bound Anglo American), Middleburg (coal South Africa), Klipspruit (coal South Africa), Alhué (gold Meridian Gold), among others.

Courses (certificate):

"Chilean Mining Commission" Competent Person, member n° 281 (which empowers to sign NI 43-101 according agreement Chile and Canada), , AusIMM member n° 230594, CIM (cyber member) nº 151994, Diplomado "Desarrollo de Habilidades Gerenciales aplicadas a la Industria Minera" CMDIC, Competent Person course in Chile & Australia for BhpBilliton, Datamine basic course (Australia), Responsibilities associated with hazardous materials, Geostatistics simulation for geological variables and grades, Economics guidelines for mining exploration in Chile (Dr. Brian Mackenzie). Geotechnical Vulcan Module training, Effective Coaching for performance improvements, Observations of workers performances, Functional Management (Time control, Costs), Applied rocks mechanics fundaments, Explosive manipulation basic course (Enaex), Oratory techniques, management, Conditional simulations in Geostatistics (medium and advanced level), Statistics and Geostatistics (Basic and Medium level), Front Line Leadership, Loss Control management, Excel (advanced), First aid training, Defensive driving course, Contractors safety management, LST(Leadership Training session), Certification as Yellow Belt in Six Sigma, English lessons with native teachers for four years, Citation of Geostatistics applied to mining (prof. C.Deutsch), Mine planning using conditional simulation.

Referees:

Mario Rossi (mrossi@geosysint.com, GeoSystems-USA), Orlando Rojas (orlando.rojas@geoestima.cl), Fernando Aguirre (<u>Fernando.Aguirre@teck.com</u>, Teck Chile, Santiago), Juan Cespedes, (<u>Juan.JL.Cespedes2@bhpbilliton.com</u>), Sergio Godoy; Geology Manager Anglo American sgodoy@anglochile.cl

Luis Aedo Sanhueza.

lsaedo@collahuasi.cl

Phone:

Office: (57) 516487 Mobile: 99696688